Guide to the Fales Manuscript Collection circa 1700-2000 MSS.001
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Letter sized boxes
  - Sladen, Douglas Brooke Wheelton, undated (Box 162, Folder 3a)
  - Slim, William, undated (Box 162, Folder 3b)
  - Sloan, William Milligan, undated (Box 162, Folder 3c)
  - Smaley, J. M., undated (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Smedley, Francis Edward, undated (Box 162, Folder 3e)
  - Smellie, William, undated (Box 162, Folder 4a)
  - Smirke, Robert, Sir, undated (Box 162, Folder 4b)
  - Smith, Albert Richard, undated (Box 162, Folder 4c)
  - Smith, Anker, undated (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - [Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: see Boxes 163-167.5.A and Legal & Oversize], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_24bd8acc952f1af88309e3d29a1fc568)
  - Smith, C. Roche, undated (Box 162, Folder 4e)
  - Smith, Charles Roach, undated (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Charlotte, undated (Box 162, Folder 5a)
  - Smith, Clark Ashton, undated (Box 162, Folder 5b)
  - Smith, Frances Hopkinson, undated (Box 162, Folder 6a)
  - Smith, Goldwin, undated (Box 162, Folder 6b)
  - Smith, John, undated (Box 162, Folder 6c)
  - Smith, Joseph P. of Urbana (Ohio) Daily Citizen, undated (Box 162, Folder 7a)
  - Smith, Logan Pearsall, undated (Box 162, Folder 7b)
  - Smith, Margaret Chase, undated (Box 162, Folder 7c)
  - Smith, Samuel Francis [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. Robert Burns and the Merry Muses of Caledonia, undated (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. Is there a Scottish Renaissance?, undated (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. King Stobo, undated (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. Kirkcaldy Lectures [1-3], undated (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. Kirkcaldy Lectures [4 & 8], undated (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: Poems (MSS.): Omens; Celebrate the Seasons, undated (Box 162.5, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. The Wallace [Act I - II], undated (Box 162.5, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. The Wallace [Act III - V], undated (Box 162.5, Folder 3)
  - Smith, William Sidney, Sir: 1 A.L.s., undated (Box 162.5, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Argles - Balston [see also Legal & Oversize], undated (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Beadon - Bryce, undated (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Carr - Colebrook, undated (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Colebrooke - Creagh, undated (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Creighton - Deane, undated (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Dedel - Fearn, undated (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Field - Gosling, undated (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Gosling - Gunning, undated (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Hadler - Ilbert, undated (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Jackson - Jowett, undated (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Kennicott - Leigh, Cholmeley, undated (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Leigh, Edward - Leigh, Emma Smith-Austen, undated (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Leigh, James Edward Austen - LeMarchant, Helen A., undated (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from LeMarchant, Sarah Eliza [Smith], undated (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Leyland - Northbrook, undated (Box 163.5, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Paget - Scott, undated (Box 163.5, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Selwyn - Seymour, Elizabeth, undated (Box 163.5, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Frances (Smith), 1805-1837 (Box 163.5, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Frances (Smith), 1838-1871 (Box 163.5, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Frances (Smith), undated (Box 163.5, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, F. M. - Seymour, Laura M. Culme, undated (Box 163.5, Folder 7)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Maria Louisa Smith Culme, 1834-1850 (Box 163.5, Folder 8)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Maria Louisa Smith Culme, 1852-1867 (Box 163.5, Folder 9)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Michael - Seymour, Sissy Culme, undated (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Augusta Spencer, 1809-1831 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Augusta Spencer, 1832-1844 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, C. - Smith, L. M., undated (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Mary, 1826-1839 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Orlando Spencer - Smith, Spencer, 1814-1830 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Spencer, 1831-1839 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Spencer - Smith, W. H., 1839-1870 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Spooner-Thring, Henry, undated (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Walgrave - Webster [see also Oversize], undated (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Wilder, Augusta Smith [see also Smith, Augusta Spencer], undated (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Wilder, Charles - Yonge, Charlotte, undated (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Unidentified, undated (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence to Hodgson, Emily (Mrs. W. B. Hodgson), undated (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Diaries [1802, 1803]: Smith, Augusta (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Diaries [1805, 1824]: Smith, Augusta (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: MS. Jamaica, 1865 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: MS. Description of South Wales, undated (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: MS. Poems, undated (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Genealogies: Smith Family, undated (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Printed Materials, undated (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Christmas Cards, undated (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Miscellaneous Greeting Cards, undated (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Miniature Newspapers, undated (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Newspaper Clipping, undated (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Silouettes [sic], undated (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Water Colors and Drawings, undated (Box 167, Folder 11)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographs: Artifacts, Bookplates, miscellaneous, undated (Box 167, Folder 12)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographs: Churches, undated (Box 167, Folder 13)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographs: Houses and People in group shots, undated (Box 167, Folder 14)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographs: Jamaica, undated (Box 167, Folder 15)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographs: Towns and Cities, undated (Box 167, Folder 16)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic: Children and Pets, undated (Box 167, Folder 17)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic: Men and Groups, undated (Box 167.5, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic: Women, undated (Box 167.5, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Spencer [8(a)], undated (Box 167.5, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Legal Documents [8(b)], undated (Box 167.5, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: MS. Funeral Procession of Seymour, Sir Michael, Rear Admiral [8(c)], undated (Box 167.5, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Song The King of Merry England [Gilfillan, Robert (1798-1850)], undated (Box 167.5, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic Album [1], undated (Box 167.5.A, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic Album [2], undated (Box 167.5.A, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic Album [3], undated (Box 167.5.A, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic Album [4], undated (Box 167.5.B, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic Album [5], undated (Box 167.5.B, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: handwritten Italian book, undated (Box 167.5.B, Folder 3)
  - Snaith, John Collis, undated (Box 168, Folder 1a)
  - Snow, C. P., undated (Box 168, Folder 1b)
  - Soder, J. H., undated (Box 168, Folder 1c)
  - Somerville, Edith Anne O'Enone, undated (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Somerville, Mary Fairfax, undated (Box 168, Folder 1e)
  - Sonon, ______?, undated (Box 168, Folder 2a)
  - Sotheby, William, undated (Box 168, Folder 2b)
  - Sothern, Edward Askew (1826-1881), undated (Box 168, Folder 2c)
  - Soutar, William: MS. Lyrics in English [1926-1933] (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Southey, Robert, undated (Box 168, Folder 4a)
  - Southworth, Emma Dorothy Eliza, undated (Box 168, Folder 4b)
  - Sparks, Jared, undated (Box 168, Folder 5a)
  - Spence, W., undated (Box 168, Folder 5b)
  - Spender, John, undated (Box 168, Folder 5c)
  - Spender, Stephen, undated (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Spielmann, Marion Harry, undated (Box 168, Folder 5e)
  - Spingarn, Joel Elias (1875-1939), undated (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Spofford, A. R., undated (Box 168, Folder 6a)
  - Spofford, Harriet P., undated (Box 168, Folder 6b)
  - Spooner, John, undated (Box 168, Folder 6c)
  - Sprague, Charles, undated (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Sprague, William Buell, undated (Box 168, Folder 6e)
  - Sprigge, Elizabeth, undated (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Spurgeon, Charles Haddon, undated (Box 168, Folder 7a)
  - Squire, John Collings, Sir, undated (Box 168, Folder 7b)
  - Stacpoole, Henry de Vere, undated (Box 168, Folder 7c)
  - Stae¨l-Holstein, Anne Louise Germaine (Necker), undated (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Stainer, John, Sir, undated (Box 168, Folder 8a)
  - Stanfield, Clarkson, undated (Box 168, Folder 8b)
  - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady, undated (Box 168, Folder 8c)
  - Starrett, Vincent, undated (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence, undated (Box 168, Folder 9a)
  - Steel, Flora Anne (Webster), undated (Box 168, Folder 9b)
  - Stein, Gertrude, undated (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - Steinbeck, John, undated (Box 168, Folder 11a)
  - Stephen, Leslie, Sir, undated (Box 168, Folder 11b)
  - Stephens, Frederic George, undated (Box 168, Folder 11c)
  - Stephens, James, undated (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Stephens, Kate, undated (Box 168, Folder 12a)
  - Stephens, Kate: Notes and Commentary to The Professor's Love-Life, undated (Box 168, Folder 12b)
  - Stepney, C. S., undated (Box 168.5, Folder 1a)
  - Stepney, Catherine, Lady, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 1b)
  - Sterling, George, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 1c)
  - Sterne, Lawrence, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 1)
  - Stevenson, Burton Egbert, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 1e)
  - Stevenson, Fanny (Van de Grift), undated (Box 168.5, Folder 1)
  - Stevenson, J. H., undated (Box 168.5, Folder 1g)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 2a)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis: Pictorial Treasure Island, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 2b)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis: Woodcuts/Proofs, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 3)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis: MSS. Music [transcript of Schubert], undated (Box 168.5, Folder 4)
  - Stewart, C. D., undated (Box 168.5, Folder 5a)
  - Stewart, D. J., undated (Box 168.5, Folder 5b)
  - Stirling-Maxwel, William, Sir, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 5c)
  - Stockley, Cynthia, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 5)
  - Stockton, Frank Richard, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 5e)
  - Stoddard, Charles Warden, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 5)
  - Stoddard, Henry, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 5g)
  - [Stoker, Bram: see Box 169], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_b52ce0f1320a029a334af690cf7e92d0)
  - Stoppard, John L., undated (Box 168.5, Folder 6a)
  - Stoppard, Richard Henry, undated (Box 168.5, Folder 6b)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): Correspondence: 2 A.L.s.; 3 Telegrams, undated (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): Correspondence to E. Robins, undated (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. The Lair of the White Worm [Chapters 1-15], undated (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. The Lair of the White Worm [Chapters 16-30], undated (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. The Lair of the White Worm [Chapters 31-41], undated (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. Under the Sunset, undated (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): Pamphlet Under the Sunset, undated (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. "Invisible Giant" in Under the Sunset, undated (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. "The Rose Prince" in Under the Sunset, undated (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. "The Shadow Builder" in Under the Sunset, undated (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. "The Wondrous Child" in Under the Sunset, undated (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - Stokes, Frances Kemble, undated (Box 170, Folder 1a)
  - Stone, David M., undated (Box 170, Folder 1b)
  - Stone, Marcus, undated (Box 170, Folder 1c)
  - Story, Emelyn, undated (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Story, William Wetmore, undated (Box 170, Folder 2a)
  - Stout, Rex, undated (Box 170, Folder 2b)
  - Stowe, Harriet Elizabeth (Beecher), undated (Box 170, Folder 2c)
  - Strachey, John St. Loe, undated (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Strachey, Lytton, undated (Box 170, Folder 2e)
  - Stratford de Radcliffe, Stratford Canning, undated (Box 170, Folder 3a)
  - Straus, Ludwig, undated (Box 170, Folder 3b)
  - [Streatfeild, Noel: see Box 171], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_6e8c4ae74cc8e75f6a1b04b4ca0508b0)
  - Street, Gladys Bertha, undated (Box 170, Folder 3c)
  - Stribling, T.S., undated (Box 170, Folder 4a)
  - Strickland, Agnes, undated (Box 170, Folder 4b)
  - Strickland, R.P., Rev., undated (Box 170, Folder 4c)
  - Strindberg, August, undated (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Strindberg, Frida, undated (Box 170, Folder 4e)
  - Stringer, Arthur, undated (Box 170, Folder 5a)
  - Strutt, Joseph, undated (Box 170, Folder 5b)
  - Sturgis, Henry, undated (Box 170, Folder 5c)
  - Sue, Euge´ne, undated (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Sullivan, Arthur, undated (Box 170, Folder 5e)
  - Sullivan, Mark, undated (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Sullivan, William, undated (Box 170, Folder 6a)
  - Sumner, Charles (1811-1874): [Choate, Rufus], undated (Box 170, Folder 6b)
  - Sunderland, D. F., undated (Box 170, Folder 6c)
  - Swanberg, W. A., undated (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Swenson, May, undated (Box 170, Folder 6e)
  - Swinburne, Algernon, undated (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Swinnerton, Frank Arthur, undated (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Symington, Andrew James, undated (Box 170, Folder 9a)
  - Symonds, John Addington, undated (Box 170, Folder 9b)
  - Symons, Alfred James Albert, undated (Box 170, Folder 9c)
  - Symons, Arthur, undated (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Streatfeild, Noel: MS. The Magic Summer Chapters 1 - 10, undated (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Streatfeild, Noel: MS. The Magic Summer Chapters 11 - 20, undated (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Streatfeild, Noel: MS. The Magic Summer Chapters 21 - 29, undated (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Tabb, John Banister (1844-1909), undated (Box 177, Folder 1a)
  - [Taine, John: see Bell, Eric Temple, Box 13.5], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_263a1c6cb539d63184677fc3016d928e)
  - Talbot, Catherine (1721-1770), undated (Box 177, Folder 1b)
  - Talfourd, Mr.: Correspondence to, undated (Box 177, Folder 1c)
  - Talfourd, Francis (1828-1862), undated (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Talfourd, Thomas Noon, Sir (1795-1854): Correspondence from [see also Dickens, Charles: MS. Prologue to Every Man in His Humour], undated (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Talfourd, Thomas Noon, Sir (1795-1854): Correspondence to, undated (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Talfourd, Thomas Noon, Sir (1795-1854): Correspondence to, undated (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Talpur, Faiz Mohammed Khan, Mir (d. 1909), undated (Box 177, Folder 5a)
  - Tarbell, Ida M. (1857-1944), undated (Box 177, Folder 5b)
  - Tarkington, (Newton) Booth (1869-1946), undated (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Tarkington, (Newton) Booth (1869-1946): MS. Song of the Bead, undated (Box 177, Folder 7a)
  - Tarkington, Susannah, undated (Box 177, Folder 7b)
  - Tate, Allen, undated (Box 177, Folder 8a)
  - Tauscher, Johanna (Gadski) (1871-1932), undated (Box 177, Folder 8b)
  - Taylor, Bayard (1825-1878), undated (Box 177, Folder 8c)
  - Taylor, Frederick: Scrapbook [including letters], undated (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - Taylor, Tom (1817-1880), undated (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Teale, Edwin Way (1899- ), undated (Box 177, Folder 11a)
  - Teasdale (Filsinger), Sara (1884-1933), undated (Box 177, Folder 11b)
  - Telford, Thomas (1757-1884), undated (Box 177, Folder 11c)
  - Tempski, Armine von, undated (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - Tenniel, John, Sir (1820-1914), undated (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - Tennyson, Alfred Lord Baron (1809-1892), undated (Box 177, Folder 13)
  - Tennyson, Alfred Lord Baron (1809-1892): MS. Crossing the Bar, undated (Box 177, Folder 14a)
  - Tennyson, Emily, undated (Box 177, Folder 14b)
  - Terhune, Albert Payson (1872-1942), undated (Box 177, Folder 15a)
  - Terhune, Mary Virginia Hawes (1830-1922) (Marion Harland, pseud.), undated (Box 177, Folder 15b)
  - Terriss, William (1847-1897), undated (Box 177, Folder 16a)
  - Terry, Ellen (Dame Alice) (1847-1928), undated (Box 177, Folder 16b)
  - Terry, Marion, undated (Box 177, Folder 16c)
  - Teuffel, Blanche Willis (Howard), von (1847-1898), undated (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Thackeray, Anne (Beecher) (d.1864), undated (Box 177, Folder 17a)
  - Thackeray, Harriet Marian (d.1875), undated (Box 177, Folder 17b)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence: A - B, undated (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence: C - D, undated (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence: E - J, undated (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence: K - P, undated (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence: Q - Z; unidentified, undated (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray?]: unidentified, undated (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray]: A - E, undated (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray]: F, undated (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray]: G - H, undated (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray]: J - L, undated (Box 178, Folder 10)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray]: M - P, undated (Box 178, Folder 11)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray]: R, undated (Box 178, Folder 12)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray]: S, undated (Box 178, Folder 13)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray]: T - Z, undated (Box 178, Folder 14)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray]: unidentified [1840-1859] (Box 178, Folder 15)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Correspondence [not in Ray]: unidentified [1860- ?], ca. 1860 (Box 178, Folder 16)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Miscellaneous A.L.s., undated (Box 178, Folder 17)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Miscellaneous A.L.s., undated (Box 178, Folder 18)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Miscellaneous A.L.s., undated (Box 178, Folder 19)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Miscellaneous A.L.s., undated (Box 178, Folder 20)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Mat. fragments, etc., undated (Box 178, Folder 21)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Drawings 1, undated (Box 178, Folder 22)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Drawings 2, undated (Box 178, Folder 23a)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): A Hundred Heads [drawing, negative, 8x10, B&W glossy], undated (Box 178, Folder 23b)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Drawings 3, undated (Box 178, Folder 24)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Drawings 4 [see also Oversize], undated (Box 178, Folder 25)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Drawings 5, undated (Box 178, Folder 26)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Drawings 6, undated (Box 178, Folder 27)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Proofs: Round About Papers w/corrections, undated (Box 178, Folder 28)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Thackerayana: Doyle, Richard: illus. for The Newcomes; Wallace: illus. for The Bedford Row Conspiracy, undated (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Thackerayana: Correspondence re W.M.T. to Johnson, Charles Plumtree, undated (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Thackerayana: Drawing "Contents: My Own Letterbox", undated (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Thackerayana: Correspondence re W.M.T.: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Thackerayana: Pictures of W.M.T. [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Thackerayana: Printed Matter, undated (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Thackerayana: Thackeray Addenda [notes removed], undated (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Thackeray's Notebook, undated (Box 179.5, Folder 1)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Advertisement Letter [Nov. 1, 1859] (Box 179.5, Folder 2)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Original MS. of part of Chapter XL of Philip [see also Fales Brit [Thackeray] for Pendennis and Thackeray [2] for French Grammar, by Delevizac, M.], undated (Box 179.5, Folder 3)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): The Dedication of W.M.T.'s Pendennis, codex, undated (Box 179.5.A, Folder 1)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Seven Original Drawings, undated (Box 179.5.A, Folder 2)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Scrapbook with MS. and Drawings, undated (Box 179.5.A, Folder 3)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Drawing, "The Lion of the Street", undated (Box 179.5.B, Folder 1)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Drawing, "Three Playing Cards", undated (Box 179.5.B, Folder 2)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): MS. and Drawing, undated (Box 179.5.B, Folder 3)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace (1811-1863): Whitey Brown Paper Mag, undated (Box 179.5.B, Folder 4)
  - Thaer, Lemuel, undated (Box 180, Folder 1a)
  - Thaxter, Celia (Leighton) (1835-1894), undated (Box 180, Folder 1b)